Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
5488 B
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
669 linear feet.
Correspondence, Rule books, Agreements, etc.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
SUBJECTS
Names:
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
Subjects:
Railroads--Employees--Labor unions--United States--Sources.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted. Please contact the Kheel Center Reference Archivist for access information.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
This forms a portion of collection #5488 B. The guide to the entire collection is available here.
Series LXVII is arranged in 7 sub-series by Union file number.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series LXVII. GRAND EXECUTIVE COUNCIL
  - Sub-Series 386-0. Grand Executive Council
    - General, 1928-1959 (Box 526, Folder 27)
    - General. Automobile Purchase Plan, 1948 (Box 526, Folder 28)
    - General, 1927 (Box 526, Folder 29)
    - General, 1926 (Box 526, Folder 30)
  - Sub-Series 386-1. Grand Executive Council
    - Sessions, 1933-1945 (Box 526, Folder 31)
    - Sessions, 1932 (Box 526, Folder 32)
    - Sessions, 1931 (Box 526, Folder 33)
    - Sessions, 1930 (Box 526, Folder 34)
    - Sessions, 1929 (Box 526, Folder 35)
    - Sessions, 1927 (Box 526, Folder 36)
    - Sessions, 1926 (Box 526, Folder 37)
  - Sub-Series 386-2. Grand Executive Council
    - Motions and Resolutions, 1931 (Box 526, Folder 38)
    - Motions and Resolutions, 1930 (Box 526, Folder 39)
    - Motions and Resolutions, 1928 (Box 526, Folder 40)
    - Motions and Resolutions, 1927 (Box 526, Folder 41)
    - Motions and Resolutions, 1925 (Box 526, Folder 42)
  - Sub-Series 386-3. Grand Executive Council
    - Minutes of Meetings, 1952 (Box 526, Folder 43)
      1952 September
    - Minutes of Meetings, 1952 (Box 526, Folder 44)
      April 22-25, 1952.
    - Minutes of Meetings, 1951 (Box 526, Folder 45)
      1951 November
    - Minutes of Meetings, 1951 (Box 526, Folder 46)
      1951 March
    - Minutes of Meetings, 1960-1962 (Box 526, Folder 47)
    - Minutes of Meetings, 1925-1949 (Box 526, Folder 48)
    - Minutes of Meetings, 1950-1951 (Box 527, Folder 1)
    - Minutes of Meetings, 1960 (Box 527, Folder 2)
      January 25-29, 1960.
    - Minutes of Meetings, 1950 (Box 527, Folder 3)
      November 13-15, 1950.
    - Minutes of Meetings, 1950 (Box 527, Folder 4)
      1950 April
    - Minutes of Meetings, 1949 (Box 527, Folder 5)
      1949 October
    - Minutes of Meetings, 1949 (Box 527, Folder 6)
      1949 April
    - Minutes of Meetings, 1948 (Box 527, Folder 7)
      1948 November
  - Sub-Series 386-4. Grand Executive Council
    - Special Meeting, 1931 (Box 527, Folder 8)
    - Special Meeting, 1933-1934 (Box 527, Folder 9)
    - Special Meeting, 1932 (Box 527, Folder 10)
    - Special Meeting, 1928 (Box 527, Folder 11)
    - Special Meeting, 1927 (Box 527, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 386-5. Grand Executive Council
    - Appeals, 1935-1957 (Box 527, Folder 13)
    - Appeals, 1960-1963 (Box 527, Folder 14)
    - Appeals. DeBorde, M.C., 1960-1961 (Box 527, Folder 15)
    - Appeals, 1927 (Box 527, Folder 16)
    - Appeals, 1926 (Box 527, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 386-6. Grand Executive Council
    - Meetings, 1961-1962 (Box 527, Folder 18)
    - Meetings, 1949-1955 (Box 527, Folder 19)
      1949-March 1955.
    - Meetings, 1943-1948 (Box 527, Folder 20)
    - Meetings. Special Meeting, 1961 (Box 527, Folder 21)
      May 2-4, 1961.
    - Meetings, 1961 (Box 527, Folder 22)
      1961 February
    - Meetings, 1955-1960 (Box 527, Folder 23)
      April 1955-60.
    - Meetings, 1960 (Box 527, Folder 24)
      1960 August
    - Meetings, 1926-1942 (Box 527, Folder 25)